JAY R. RAUTEL

Frontend Developer



9146635275

Gumgaon Mine Khapa, Saoner, Nagpur, 441101

25/01/2001

in Linkedin

GitHub

SKILLS

HTML, CSS SCSS

JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY

REACT.JS, REDUX, FORMIK

BOOTSTRAP, MATERIAL-UI

PERSONAL STRENGTH

Teamworking

Leadership

Dedicated to work

INTERESTS

- · Star Gazing
- Volleyball, Football

LANGUAGES

· Hindi, Marathi, English

CERTIFICATE

AIRC 2020 Season_4

Participated in All India Racing Championship

PROFILE

"Hello, I'm Jay, a front-end developer with a passion for creating engaging and user-friendly web experiences. With expertise in some of the frontend tech stack, I enjoy crafting intuitive and visually appealing interfaces that enhance user interactions.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Engineering (Mechanical),

Jhulelal Institute Of Technology, Nagpur 08/2018 – 08/2022 | Nagpur, India

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Development Training,

Reflection Training Academy (6 months Training) 2022 | Nagpur, India

Web Developer Trainee, Null Classs

11/2022 - 05/2023 | India

Web Developer Intern, TwiLearn Edutech

08/2023 - 09/2023 | India

PROJECTS

Templates 🛮

- Burger House Template
- Ford Template

Gym Management System 🗗

Features:

- · Login & Signup
- Add/View/Delete member
- Bill generation

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Stop & Shop, *E-Commerce Site* □

Features:

- · Login and signup functionality
- RESTful API creation & integration
- Product Search functionality
- Product filters
- Cart functionality

Tech Stack: React.js, Scss, React-Formik, Redux-Toolkit, Material-UI, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express.js.